I should've known that you would
be here, Professor McGonagall.
Good evening, Professor Dumbledore.
Are the rumors true, Albus?
I'm afraid so, professor.
The good and the bad.
- And the boy?
- Hagrid is bringing him.
Is it wise to trust Hagrid
with something so important?
Professor, I would trust Hagrid
with my life.
Professor Dumbledore, sir.
Professor McGonagall.
- No problems, I trust, Hagrid?
- No, sir.
Little tyke fell asleep
as we were flying over Bristol.
Try not to wake him.
There you go.
Do you really think it's safe,
leaving him with these people?
I've watched them all day.
They're the worst sort of Muggles.
- They really are--
- The only family he has.
He'll be famous. Every child
in our world will know his name.
Exactly.
He's far better off growing up
away from all of that.
Until he's ready.
There, there, Hagrid.
It's not really goodbye, after all.